SUNY Faculty Senate Documents /3093
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
SUNY Faculty Senate Documents
1971-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
State University of New York (SUNY)
/3093
0.33 cubic feet
0.3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists primarily of Faculty Senate minutes.
7929419
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 15, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3081: SUNY Files 4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files 4075: Robert Doherty Papers
State University of New York.; State University of New York. University Faculty Senate.
7929419
- Fall Meeting: University Faculty Senate, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- To: Members of the University Faculty Senate, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Instructions Winter Meeting University Faculty Senate, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- State University and Senate Professional Association - Articles 33 and 34 of the Agreement, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Questionnaires, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Grievance Claims Prior to August 31, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Questionnaires for Determining Faculty Priorities, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Faculty Senate Minutes College at Alfred October 22-23, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Faculty Senate Minutes College at Buffalo 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Summary of Proceedings Center at Stony Brook January 31-February 1, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Faculty Senate Minutes AG and Tech College at Canton November 1-2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Winter Meeting University Faculty Senate, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Resolutions adopted at the 48th Regional Meeting of the University Faculty Senate, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Agenda Materials University Faculty Senate, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- SUNY Faculty Senate Committee on Graduate Program, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Health Science and Health Affairs Committee of the SUNY Senate, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)